Save the day.
Shotgun Wedding is a action, comedy, romance film directed by Jason Moore.
Darcy and Tom gather their families for the ultimate destination wedding but when the entire
party is taken hostage, “’Til Death Do Us Part” takes on a whole new meaning.
Now, Darcy and Tom must save their loved ones—if
they don’t kill each other first.
Darcy Rivera, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Tom Fowler, played by Josh Duhamel.
Sean Hawkins, played by Lenny Kravitz.
Carol Fowler, played by Jennifer Coolidge.
Renata Ortiz, played by Sônia Braga.
Robert Rivera, played by Cheech Marin.
Shotgun Wedding is a 2022 American romantic action comedy film
directed by Jason Moore and written by Mark Hammer.
It stars Jennifer Lopez, Josh Duhamel, Sônia Braga, Jennifer
Coolidge, Lenny Kravitz, and Cheech Marin.
After being filmed from February to April 2021 in Boston and the Dominican Republic, Shotgun Wedding was released in
Singapore on December 28, 2022, and was released on January 27, 2023, by Amazon Studios via Prime Video.
The film explores themes of pirate gang, ex fiancé,
philippines, wedding, hostage situation.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.